Charles Mingus Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music (Box 1-44)
  - Manuscript Music (Box 1-29, Box 32-44)
    - Original Music Manuscripts (Box 1-28, Box 32-44)
      - Goodbye pork pie hat., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; various sizes; Note: Copyist's manuscripts in ink and pencil; includes photocopies.; Reference no.: 101. (Box-folder 8/1)
      - Goodbye pork pie hat (#18)., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 31.5 cm.; Note: Copyists' manuscripts in ink and pencil.; Reference no.: 032. (Box-folder 8/2)
      - Goodbye pork pie hat., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 30 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscripts in ink and pencil.; Reference no.: 34. (Box-folder 8/3)
      - Gotta., Condensed score; 3 p.; 31.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil. (Box-folder 8/4)
      - The grass is greener / lyrics by Charles Mingus; music by Paul M. Jeffrey., Lead sheet; 2 p.; 27 cm.; Note: Photocopy of copyist's manuscript.; Access points: Jeffrey, Paul M. Mingus, Charles (Box-folder 8/5)
      - Gregorian chant., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 32 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil. At bottom: © February, 1976, Jazz Workshop, Inc. (Box-folder 8/6)
      - Gunslinging bird., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 28 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph.; Reference no.: 241. (Box-folder 8/7)
      - Gunslinging bird / Sy Johnson, arr., Guitar 1 part; 1 p.; 32 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in ink.; Reference no.: 241.; Access points: Johnson, Sy (Box-folder 8/8)
      - Half-mast inhibition. See also: Mingus dance no. 5, Full score; 24 leaves; 34.5 x 44.5 cm.; Note: Holograph and copyist's manuscript in pencil; last two pages arranged by Sy Johnson.; Reference no.: 120. (Box-folder 36/4)
      - Hamps new blues., Lead sheet; 1 lv.; 35.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. At bottom: © December, 1976, Jazz Workshop, Inc. (Box-folder 8/9)
      - Harris + Mingus fingers. See also: Mingus fingers, Full score; 18 leaves; 35.5 x 40.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil.; Reference no.: 052. (Box-folder 36/5)
      - Harris + Mingus fingers (A-170). See also: Mingus fingers, Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 30.5 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscripts in ink and pencil.; Reference no.: 052. (Box-folder 8/10)
      - Hatian fight song / Sy Johnson, arr. See also: Mingus dances, no. 9, Lead sheet; 1 p.; 32 cm.; Note: Manuscript in ink on transparent paper by Sy Johnson.; Reference no.: 239.; Access points: Johnson, Sy (Box-folder 8/11)
      - Heart's beat and shades in physical embraces., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 31 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. At bottom: © December, 1975, Jazz Workshop, Inc. (Box-folder 8/12)
      - Herricane Sue [sic] / Sy Johnson, arr., Full score; 28 leaves; 35.5 x 43.5 cm.; Note: Manuscript in pencil by Sy Johnson.; Reference no.: 147.; Access points: Johnson, Sy (Box-folder 36/6)
      - Hobo-ho., Lead sheet; 2 leaves; 35.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. Date at bottom of p. one: © Jan., 1975; date at bottom of p. two: © April, 1972, Jazz Workshop, Inc., New York, New York.; Reference no.: 035. (Box-folder 8/13)
      - Hobo-ho., Full score; 25 leaves; 30.5 x 48.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil and ink.; Reference no.: 035. (Box-folder 36/7)
      - Hobo-ho., Full score; 26 leaves; 28.5 x 44.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph score.; Reference no.: 035. (Box-folder 36/8)
      - Hobo-ho (#25)., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm. (in 2 folders).; Note: Copyist's manuscripts in ink and pencil.; Reference no.: 35. (Box-folder 8/14-15)
      - Hog callin' blues., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 33.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. At bottom: © February, 1976, Jazz Workshop, Inc., NY, NY. (Box-folder 8/16)
      - Hora decubitis., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 35.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. At bottom: © Jazz Workshop, Inc., Nov., 1976. (Box-folder 8/17)
      - Hot dogs for lunch., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscripts in ink; includes photocopy of tenor saxophone part.; Reference no.: 036. (Box-folder 8/18)
      - Hot town., Full score; 13 leaves; 34.5 x 44 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil.; Reference no.: 112. (Box-folder 37/1)
      - Hot town., Full score; 13 leaves; 35 x 43 cm.; Note: Deshan (thermofax) copy of copyist's manuscript (Ref. no. 112).; Reference no.: 280. (Box-folder 37/2)
      - Hurricane Sue. See also: The I of Hurricane Sue, Condensed score (incomplete); 1 leaf; 39.5 x 43 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in pencil.; Reference no.: 147. (Box-folder 43/6)
      - Hurt ego., Chord chart; 1 p.; 31.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil. At bottom of page is trumpet part, in ink, to an untitled piece; on verso is piano part, in pencil, to an untitled piece. (Box-folder 8/19)
      - I just don't care., Bass part; 1 p.; 28 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil. At bottom and on verso: the tunes Whatever happened to U; Angela; 5:00 Whistle. (Box-folder 8/20)
      - The I of Hurricane Sue., Lead sheet; 2 leaves; 30.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in ink on transparent paper.; Reference no.: 037. (Box-folder 8/21)
      - The I of Hurricane Sue., Condensed score; 2 p.; 28 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil and incomplete photocopy of same. On verso of holograph: bass part for the tune Orange was the color of her dress, then blue silk; holograph in ink, and at bottom, the continuation of I of Hurricane Sue. in pencil.; Reference no.: 037. (Box-folder 8/22)
      - The I of Hurricane Sue., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; various sizes.; Note: Holographs and copyist's manuscripts in ink with pencil markings, and photocopies. The word "Hurricane" is spelled "Herricane" on some parts.; Reference no.: 142. (Box-folder 8/23)
      - [The I of Hurricane Sue]., Instrumental parts (string parts only); pagination varies; 33.5 cm.; Note: Photocopies of copyist's manuscripts.; Reference no.: 037. (Box-folder 8/24)
      - I x love., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 28 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. Marked at head: 145. In typescript: Di Charles Mingus - Edizioni Blue Team Music. (Box-folder 8/25)
      - I'm a lonesome woman., Song lyrics; 1 p.; 31.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil. (Box-folder 9/1)
      - Intermit., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 18 x 20 cm.; Note: Holograph in ink.; Reference no.: 234. (Box-folder 9/2)
      - Intermit., Instrumental parts, tenor and piano only; 1 p.; 31.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil and ink. On verso: Chord progressions for the tune Pensativa.; Reference no.: 234. (Box-folder 9/3)
      - Invisible lady., Lead sheet; 2 leaves; 27.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. On both leaves: © January, 1975, Jazz Workshop, Inc. (Box-folder 9/4)
      - Invisible lady., Cello solo; 1 p.; 32 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil. On verso: instrumental part for untitled piece. (Box-folder 9/5)
      - Isabele's table dance. See also: Ysabel's table dance, Instrumental parts; pagination varies; various sizes.; Note: Holographs in ink and pencil with holograph ink and pencil markings; includes photocopies with markings in pencil and ink. Alternate title scratched out: Tijuana's table dance.; Reference no.: 213. (Box-folder 9/6)
      - Isabel's table dance / Sy Johnson, arr. See also: Ysabel's table dance, Full score; 11 leaves; 32 cm.; Note: Manuscript in pencil by Sy Johnson.; Reference no.: 212.; Access points: Johnson, Sy (Box-folder 37/3)
      - Isabele's table dance / Sy Johnson, arr. See also: Ysabel's table dance, Instrumental parts (guitar only); pagination varies; various sizes.; Note: Holographs in ink and includes photocopy of same.; Reference no.: 212.; Access points: Johnson, Sy (Box-folder 9/7)
      - [It's] nice of you to [have come to my funeral]., Full score; 1 p.; 31 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil.; Reference no.: 038. (Box-folder 9/8)
      - It's nice of you to have come to my funeral., Instrumental parts; various sizes; 32 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscripts in ink, pencil, and marker.; Reference no.: 038. (Box-folder 9/9)
      - [Jack the Bear]., Bass part; 1 p.; 32 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil.; Reference no.: 244. (Box-folder 9/10)
      - Jackie's blues., Piano-vocal score; 2 leaves; 31.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil. (Box-folder 9/11)
      - Jell Roll., Lead sheet (in bass cleff); 2 leaves; 32 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in ink on transparent paper. At Bottom in pencil: © May 1956, Jazz Workshop, Inc.; Reference no.: 039. (Box-folder 9/12)
      - (Jelly Roll): aka "my Jelly Roll soul"., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 35.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph with markings in ink and felt-tip marker. In red ink: "This corresponds to the ABC version, not the CBS." At bottom: © Jan. 1975, Jan. 1977 Jazz Workshop, Inc., NYC, NY.; Reference no.: 136. (Box-folder 9/13)
      - Jelly Roll / Sy Johnson, arr., Full score; 8 leaves; 28 x 43 cm.; Note: Manuscript in pencil by Sy Johnson.; Reference no.: 136.; Access points: Johnson, Sy (Box-folder 37/4)
      - Jive five floor four (remember Rockefeller at Attica) [cell block F is Nazi U.S.A.]., Condensed score; 2 p.; 32 cm.; Note: Holograph ms. in pencil.; Reference no.: 040. (Box-folder 9/14)
      - Jive five floor four (remember Rockefeller at Attica) [cell block F is Nazi U.S.A.]., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscripts in ink. At bottom of piano part: © Nov. 1974, Jazz Workshop, Inc.; Reference no.: 040. (Box-folder 9/15)
      - John Doe., Instrumental parts ("baritone" and "1st bone" parts only); pagination varies; 30.5 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscripts in ink; lyrics included on each parts.; Reference no.: 168. (Box-folder 9/16)
      - Juice see: Winds (BOX: 28/14)
      - Jump Monk / Sy Johnson, arr., Full score; 27 leaves; 35.5 x 43.5 cm.; Note: Manuscript in pencil by Sy Johnson.; Reference no.: 041.; Access points: Johnson, Sy (Box-folder 37/5)
      - Jump Monk (#2)., Full score; 26 leaves; 36 x 42 cm.; Note: Manuscript in pencil, hand unknown.; Reference no.: 041. (Box-folder 37/6)
      - Jump Monk (#2)., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscripts in ink and pencil, hand unknown.; Reference no.: 041. (Box-folder 9/17)
      - Just for laughs saps., Lead sheet; 2 p.; 30.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil.; Reference no.: 042. (Box-folder 9/18)
      - Just for laughs saps., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 30.5 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscripts in ink. At bottom: © November 1974, Jazz Workshop, Inc.; Reference no.: 042. (Box-folder 9/19)
      - Lass., Guitar and bass parts; 2 p.; 32 cm.; Note: Holographs in ink and pencil. (Box-folder 9/20)
      - Laura., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm.; Note: Holographs in pencil.; Reference no.: 196. (Box-folder 9/21)
      - Letter ashes., Instrumental parts; 4 p.; 32 cm.; Note: Holographs in pencil. (Box-folder 9/22)
      - Little Royal suite., Lead sheet; 2 leaves; 28 cm.; Note: Photocopy of copyist's manuscript. At head: June 1975, Jazz Workshop, Inc., NYC, NY.; Reference no.: 043, 116. (Box-folder 9/23)
      - Little Royal suite (#26)., Condensed score; 25 leaves; 39.5 cm.; Note: Manuscript in pencil by Teo Macero (Intro., pages 1-2); the remainder arranged and scored by C. Mingus. Pages 1 and 2 are penned in full score form.; Reference no.: 043. (Box-folder 37/7)
      - Little Royal suite (#26)., Full score, "coda"; 3 leaves; 35.5 x 43 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in pencil by Sy Johnson.; Reference no.: 043. (Box-folder 37/8)
      - Little Royal suite (#26)., Full score, "insert"; 9 leaves; 35.5 x 43 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in pencil by Sy Johnson.; Reference no.: 043. (Box-folder 37/9)
      - Little Royal suite (#26)., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm. (2 folders).; Note: Copyist's manuscripts in ink and pencil.; Reference no.: 043. (Box-folder 9/24-25)
      - Lonesome woman blues., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 30 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. Marked at head: 148. In typescript: Di Charles Mingus - Edizioni Blue Team Music. (Box-folder 10/1)
      - Los Mariachis., Lead sheet; 2 leaves; 35.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. (Box-folder 10/2)
      - Love chant., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 30.5 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in ink. At bottom: © Chaz Mar Music, 19--. (Box-folder 10/3)
      - Love is a dangerous necessity., Instrumental parts (incomplete); 3 leaves; 32 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscripts in ink. At bottom: © June 1972, Jazz Workshop, Inc., NYC, NY.; Reference no.: 242. (Box-folder 10/4)
      - Love's fury., Full score (incomplete); 1 p.; 30.5 x 40.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil.; Reference no.: 044. (Box-folder 37/10)
      - Love's fury., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm.; Note: Holographs in ink and pencil.; Reference no.: 044. (Box-folder 10/5)
      - Make believe., Full score; 9 leaves; 28 x 35.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil.; Reference no.: 062. (Box-folder 10/6)
      - Make believe., Full score (incomplete); 9 leaves; 30.5 x 40.5 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in pencil. Last page of score missing.; Reference no.: 063. (Box-folder 37/11)
      - Make believe., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 31.5 cm.; Note: Holographs in ink and pencil.; Reference no.: 062. (Box-folder 10/7)
      - Make believe., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 31.5 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscripts in ink and pencil.; Reference no.: 063. (Box-folder 10/8)
      - Make believe., Song lyrics; 3 p.; 31.5 cm.; Holograph in pencil.; Reference no.: 062, 063. (Box-folder 10/9)
      - Make me know it., Full score; 12 leaves; 34.5 x 43.5 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in pencil.; Reference no.: 104. (Box-folder 37/12)
      - Make me know it., Full score; 12 leaves; 35.5 x 43.5 cm.; Note: Deshan (thermofax) copy of manuscript score.; Reference no.: 284. (Box-folder 37/13)
      - Make me know it., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscripts in ink.; Reference no.: 104, 284. (Box-folder 10/10)
      - The nan who never sleeps / by Charles Mingus and Sy Johnson., Full score; 9 p.; 34 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil and ink.; Reference no.: 048.; Access points: Johnson, Sy Mingus, Charles (Box-folder 10/11)
      - The man who never sleeps / by Charles Mingus and Sy Johnson., Condensed score; 3 leaves; 28 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph.; Reference no.: 204.; Access points: Johnson, Sy Mingus, Charles (Box-folder 10/12)
      - The man who never sleeps / by Charles Mingus and Sy Johnson., Lead sheets; 3 leaves; 33 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscripts in ink.; Reference no.: 048.; Access points: Johnson, Sy Mingus, Charles (Box-folder 10/13)
      - The man who never sleeps / by Charles Mingus and Sy Johnson., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; various sizes.; Note: Holographs and copyist's manuscripts in ink and pencil.; Reference no.: 048.; Access points: Johnson, Sy Mingus, Charles (Box-folder 10/14)
      - Meditation #15)., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm.; Note: Holographs in ink and pencil.; Reference no.: 049. (Box-folder 10/15)
      - Meditations for Moses., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 35.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. At bottom: November 1976, © Jazz Workshop, Inc. (Box-folder 10/16)
      - Meditations on integration., Lead sheet; 2 leaves; 35.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. (Box-folder 10/17)
      - Mike & Tike., Lead sheet; 3 p.; 27 cm.; Note: Photocopy of copyist's manuscript. (Box-folder 10/18)
      - Mind-readers convention., Condensed score; 7 p.; 32 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. (Box-folder 10/19)
      - Mind-readers convention., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm.; Note: Holographs in ink and pencil. (Box-folder 10/20)
      - Mingus dances. No. 1: Pithecanthropus erectus / Alan Raph, arr., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm. (folder 1 of 2).; Note: Ozalids of copyists' manuscripts in ink with pencil markings.; Reference no.: 246.; Access points: Raph, Alan (Box-folder 10/21)
      - Mingus dances. No. 1: Pithecanthropus erectus / Alan Raph, arr., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm. (folder 2 of 2).; Note: Ozalids of copyists' manuscripts in ink with pencil markings.; Reference no.: 246.; Access points: Raph, Alan (Box-folder 11/1)
      - Mingus dances. No. 1: Pithecanthropus erectus / Alan Raph, arr., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 28 cm. (3 folders).; Note: Photocopies of copyist's manuscripts.; Reference no.: 246.; Access points: Raph, Alan (Box-folder 11/2-4)
      - Mingus dances. No. 2: O.P. (Oscar Pettiford) / Jaki Byard, arr., Full score; 20 p.; 34 cm.; Note: Holograph in ink and pencil; performance notes written throughout the score.; Reference no.: 247.; Access points: Mingus, Charles Byard, Jaki (Box-folder 11/5)
      - Mingus dances. No. 2: O.P. (Oscar Pettiford) / Alan Raph, arr., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm. (2 folders).; Note: Ozalids of copyists' manuscripts in ink with pencil markings.; Reference no.: 247.; Access points: Raph, Alan (Box-folder 11/6-7)
      - Mingus dances. No. 2: O.P. (Oscar Pettiford) / Alan Raph, arr., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 28 cm. (2 folders).; Note: Photocopies of copyists' manuscripts.; Reference no.: 247.; Access points: Raph, Alan (Box-folder 11/8-9)
      - Mingus dances. No. 3: Myself when I am real / Alan Raph, arr., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm. (3 folders).; Note: Ozalids of copyists' manuscripts in ink with pencil markings.; Reference no.: 248.; Access points: Raph, Alan (Box-folder 12/1-3)
      - Mingus dances. No. 3: Myself when I am real / Alan Raph, arr., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 28 cm. (3 folders).; Note: Photocopies of copyists' manuscripts.; Reference no.: 248.; Access points: Raph, Alan (Box-folder 12/4-6)
      - Mingus dances. No. 4: Freedom / Alan Raph, arr., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm. (2 folders).; Note: Ozalids of copyists' manuscripts in ink with pencil markings.; Reference no.: 250.; Access points: Raph, Alan (Box-folder 13/1-2)
      - Mingus dances. No. 4: Freedom / Alan Raph, arr., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 28 cm. (2 folders).; Note: Photocopies of copyist's manuscripts.; Reference no.: 250.; Access points: Raph, Alan (Box-folder 13/3-4)
      - Mingus dances. No. 5: Half-mast inhibition., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 29.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. Marked at head: 142. In typescript: Di Charles Mingus - Edizioni Blue Team Music.; Reference no.: 251. (Box-folder 13/5)
      - Mingus dances. No. 5: Half mast inhibition ("ballet suite") / Jaki Byard, arr., Full score; 18 leaves; 33 cm.; Note: Photocopy of copyist's manuscript in ink, reversed.; Reference no.: 251.; Access points: Byard, Jaki (Box-folder 13/6)
      - Mingus dances. No. 5: Half mast inhibition., Condensed score; 8 p.; 31 cm.; Note: Holograph in ink and pencil.; Reference no.: 251. (Box-folder 13/7)
      - Mingus dances. No. 5: Half mast inhibition., Piano-conductors' score; 3 leaves; 31 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil.; Reference no.: 251. (Box-folder 13/8)
      - Mingus dances. No. 5: Half mast inhibition., Piano transcription; 7 leaves; 35.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph.; Reference no.: 251. (Box-folder 13/9)
      - Mingus dances. No. 5: Half-mast inhibition / Alan Raph, arr., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm. (3 folders).; Note: Ozalids of copyist's manuscripts in ink and pencil.; Reference no.: 251.; Access points: Raph, Alan (Box-folder 13/10-12)
      - Mingus dances. No. 5: Half-mast inhibition / Alan Raph, arr., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 28 cm. (3 folders).; Note: Photocopies of copyist's manuscripts.; Reference no.: 251.; Access points: Raph, Alan (Box-folder 14/1-3)
      - Mingus dances. No. 6: Dizzy's moods / Alan Raph, arr., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm. (2 folders).; Note: Ozalids of copyist's manuscript in ink and pencil.; Reference no.: 252.; Access points: Raph, Alan (Box-folder 14/4-5)
      - Mingus dances. No. 6: Dizzy's moods / Alan Raph, arr., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 28 cm. (2 folders).; Note: Photocopies of copyist's manuscripts.; Reference no.: 252.; Access points: Raph, Alan (Box-folder 14/6-7)
      - Mingus dances. No. 7: Alice on wonderland (INA)., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 31 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil. On verso: the tune Boogie-woogie.; Reference no.: 253. (Box-folder 14/8)
      - Mingus dances. No. 7: Alice in wonderland (ballad)., Chord chart; 1 p.; 31.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in ink. On verso: the tunes Nostalgia on Times Square; Shadows, and Girl of my dreams.; Reference no.: 253. (Box-folder 14/9)
      - Mingus dances. No. 7: Diane., Lead sheet (I); 1 p.; 30.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil.; Reference no.: 253. (Box-folder 14/10)
      - Mingus dances. No. 7: Diane., Lead sheet (II); 1 p.; 30.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in ink.; Reference no.: 253. (Box-folder 14/11)
      - Mingus dances. No. 7: Diane., Lead sheet (III); 1 p.; 28 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph.; Reference no.: 253. (Box-folder 14/12)
      - Mingus dances. No. 7: Diane., Chord chart; 1 p.; 31.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in ink.; Reference no.: 253. (Box-folder 14/13)
      - Mingus dances. No. 7: Diane (ballet suite) / Jaki Byard, arr., Full score (incomplete); 7 p.; 34 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in pencil.; Reference no.: 128.; Access points: Byard, Jaki (Box-folder 14/14)
      - Mingus dances. No. 7: Diane (Alice's wonderland)., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; various sizes.; Note: Holographs in ink and pencil and photocopy of one instrumental part. On verso of the trumpet part: the tune Prayer meeting.; Reference no.: 221. (Box-folder 14/15)
      - Mingus dances. No. 7: Diane / Alan Raph, arr., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 31.5 cm. (2 folders).; Note: Copyist's manuscripts in ink with pencil and crayon markings.; Reference no.: 253.; Access points: Raph, Alan (Box-folder 14/16-17)
      - Mingus dances. No. 7: Diane / Alan Raph, arr., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 28 cm. (2 folders).; Note: Photocopies of copyist's manuscripts.; Reference no.: 253.; Access points: Raph, Alan (Box-folder 15/1-2)
      - Mingus dances. No. 7: Dianeland (Eatland; Mingus, Op. 1959)., Condensed score; 14 p.; 36 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in ink in unknown hand with pencil holograph markings. Three titles at head: 1) Dianeland; 2) Eatland; 3) Mingus - Opus 1959.; Reference no.: 253. (Box-folder 15/3)
      - Mingus dances. No. 7: Dianeland., Full score; [23] leaves; 21.5 x 28 cm.; Note: Photocopy of copyist's manuscript with red ink and pencil markings; unknown hand. Laid in: First page of manuscript full score in ink on transparent paper; unknown hand.; Reference no.: 253. (Box-folder 15/4)
      - Mingus dances. No. 7: Dianeland (adagio ma non troppo) / Alan Raph, arr., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm. (4 folders).; Note: Copyist's manuscripts in ink with pencil and crayon markings.; Reference no.: 253.; Access points: Raph, Alan (Box-folder 15/5-8)
      - Mingus dances. No. 8: Ysabel's table dance / by Charles Mingus and Alan Raph; Sy Johnson, arr., Lead sheet; 3 leaves; 30 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. At bottom of third p.: © Jazz Workshop, Inc., November 1976.; Reference no.: 254.; Access points: Johnson, Sy Mingus, Charles Raph, Alan (Box-folder 16/1)
      - Mingus dances. No. 8: Ysabel's table dance / by Charles Mingus and Alan Raph; Sy Johnson, arr., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm. (2 folders).; Note: Copyist's manuscripts in ink and pencil.; Reference no.: 097.; Access points: Johnson, Sy Mingus, Charles Raph, Alan (Box-folder 16/2-3)
      - Mingus dances. No. 8: Ysabel's table dance / Alan Raph, arr., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 28 cm. (2 folders).; Note: Photocopies of copyist's manuscripts.; Reference no.: 254.; Access points: Raph, Alan (Box-folder 16/4-5)
      - Mingus dances. No. 9: Haitian fight song / by Charles Mingus and Alan Raph., Full score; 5 leaves; 31.5 cm.; Note: Manuscript in pencil by Sy Johnson.; Reference no.: 255.; Access points: Mingus, Charles Raph, Alan (Box-folder 16/6)